<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MPCNC on SwampWire Creations</title>
    <link>https://www.swampwirecreations.com/projects/mpcnc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in MPCNC on SwampWire Creations</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2018 23:17:25 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.swampwirecreations.com/projects/mpcnc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Getting Better</title>
      <link>https://www.swampwirecreations.com/projects/mpcnc/getting-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2020 10:15:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.swampwirecreations.com/projects/mpcnc/getting-better/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After a two week hiatus from the MPCNC, I got the itch to get back to making things. I wanted to salvage the spoilboard as much as I could, level it out, and create a few clamps to making workpiece holding a little easier.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making a Spoilboard and Breaking Things</title>
      <link>https://www.swampwirecreations.com/projects/mpcnc/spoilboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 08:17:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.swampwirecreations.com/projects/mpcnc/spoilboard/</guid>
      <description>In the process of creating a spoilboard for the MPCNC, I came across several lingering issues with the machine that needed to be resolved. It ended up being an opportunity to correct a bunch of broken bits, tighten up nuts and bolts that had loosened, and come to terms with an accuracy problem I had been ignoring.
This project also gave me a chance to try a new method of documentation, and learn a lot about what works and doesn&amp;rsquo;t work for my creative workflow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Router Upgrade</title>
      <link>https://www.swampwirecreations.com/projects/mpcnc/router-upgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 06:45:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.swampwirecreations.com/projects/mpcnc/router-upgrade/</guid>
      <description>After a few years of rebuilds, teardowns, and tool changes, I am finally adding a router to my MPCNC. I have been wanting to work more with sheet material like wood, acrylic, and even aluminum if I can get the hang of using this tool.
Router Choice and Prints For a router, V1 Engineering recommend the Dewalt 660, a 5.0 Amp, handheld rotary tool that operates at 30,000 rpm with an included 1/8&amp;quot; collet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MPCNC Initial Build</title>
      <link>https://www.swampwirecreations.com/projects/mpcnc/initial-build/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 23:18:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.swampwirecreations.com/projects/mpcnc/initial-build/</guid>
      <description>After a few months of going back and forth on this idea, I decided to pull the trigger and build the Mostly Printed CNC (MPCNC). It is a CNC platform that can be assembled out of inexpensive electronics and hardware, EMT conduit, and 3d printed components.
Ryan at V1 Engineering sells a kit with all the electronics and hardware, leaving me to source a table, conduit, and print the parts. While waiting for the kit to arrive, I started the long process of printing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
