<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tabletop on SwampWire Creations</title>
    <link>https://www.swampwirecreations.com/tags/tabletop/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tabletop on SwampWire Creations</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2020 15:18:49 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.swampwirecreations.com/tags/tabletop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sate Display Piece</title>
      <link>https://www.swampwirecreations.com/blog/sate-display-piece/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2020 15:18:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.swampwirecreations.com/blog/sate-display-piece/</guid>
      <description>Slow Death Games is an indie game company that sells the Starbreach dice and rulebook, along with some awesome punk / youth subculture minis for their game &amp;ldquo;Wild in the Streets&amp;rdquo;. A few months ago on Instagram, they announced they were throwing some free stickers into new orders. I figured it was time to pull the trigger and order some minis. Yes, free stickers are what got me. In particular, the &amp;ldquo;Love Miniatures, Hate Fascism&amp;rdquo; piece.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Painting Minis and More Casting</title>
      <link>https://www.swampwirecreations.com/blog/week-in-review-002/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 17:08:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.swampwirecreations.com/blog/week-in-review-002/</guid>
      <description>This has been a week with a lot of painting, a little casting, and a bit of thinking about future projects.
Painting Finished Tank Early in the week, I was able to wrap up my Schrek tank build, which gave me a chance to get some experience in basing. The base seen above was the third iteration, where I finally got the spacing between the dirt piles right. This allowed the tank sat on the base instead of floating above the rocks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magnets, Casting, and Real Hobby Paint</title>
      <link>https://www.swampwirecreations.com/blog/week-in-review-001/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 06:21:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.swampwirecreations.com/blog/week-in-review-001/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a pretty productive week, and I got a chance to try out a bunch of new things and get some ideas for future projects a bit outside my norm. Here&amp;rsquo;s a quick recap of what I&amp;rsquo;ve been up to this week:
Magnets, Painting with Vallejo, and Basing To make my growing Battletech collection a bit more modular (and to keep from making/buying too many minis) I have been toying with the idea of swappable turrets and weapons for my pieces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Part Mold Making</title>
      <link>https://www.swampwirecreations.com/blog/two-part-mold-making/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.swampwirecreations.com/blog/two-part-mold-making/</guid>
      <description>Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to take a 3d printed tabletop miniature and replicate it with a two part mold. This will speed of production of a part that would normally take two to three hours, and give us the freedom of different materials and colors.
Two part molds allow us to cast more complex shapes than a one part, or open-face, mold. This open face creates a flat surface on the piece we are making.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
